export const mathQuizzes = {
   addition: {
     "1": [
       {
         question: "1 + 1",
         answer: "2"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 2",
         answer: "3"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 3",
         answer: "4"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 4",
         answer: "5"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 5",
         answer: "6"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 6",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 7",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 8",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 9",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 10",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 11",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "1 + 12",
         answer: "13"
       }
     ],
     "2": [
       {
         question: "2 + 1",
         answer: "3"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 2",
         answer: "4"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 3",
         answer: "5"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 4",
         answer: "6"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 5",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 6",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 7",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 8",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 9",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 10",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 11",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "2 + 12",
         answer: "14"
       }
     ],
     "3": [
       {
         question: "3 + 1",
         answer: "4"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 2",
         answer: "5"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 3",
         answer: "6"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 4",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 5",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 6",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 7",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 8",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 9",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 10",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 11",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "3 + 12",
         answer: "15"
       }
     ],
     "4": [
       {
         question: "4 + 1",
         answer: "5"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 2",
         answer: "6"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 3",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 4",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 5",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 6",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 7",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 8",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 9",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 10",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 11",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "4 + 12",
         answer: "16"
       }
     ],
     "5": [
       {
         question: "5 + 1",
         answer: "6"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 2",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 3",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 4",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 5",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 6",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 7",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 8",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 9",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 10",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 11",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "5 + 12",
         answer: "17"
       }
     ],
     "6": [
       {
         question: "6 + 1",
         answer: "7"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 2",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 3",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 4",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 5",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 6",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 7",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 8",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 9",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 10",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 11",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "6 + 12",
         answer: "18"
       }
     ],
     "7": [
       {
         question: "7 + 1",
         answer: "8"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 2",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 3",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 4",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 5",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 6",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 7",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 8",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 9",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 10",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 11",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "7 + 12",
         answer: "19"
       }
     ],
     "8": [
       {
         question: "8 + 1",
         answer: "9"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 2",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 3",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 4",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 5",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 6",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 7",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 8",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 9",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 10",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 11",
         answer: "19"
       },
       {
         question: "8 + 12",
         answer: "20"
       }
     ],
     "9": [
       {
         question: "9 + 1",
         answer: "10"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 2",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 3",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 4",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 5",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 6",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 7",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 8",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 9",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 10",
         answer: "19"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 11",
         answer: "20"
       },
       {
         question: "9 + 12",
         answer: "21"
       }
     ],
     "10": [
       {
         question: "10 + 1",
         answer: "11"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 2",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 3",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 4",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 5",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 6",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 7",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 8",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 9",
         answer: "19"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 10",
         answer: "20"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 11",
         answer: "21"
       },
       {
         question: "10 + 12",
         answer: "22"
       }
     ],
     "11": [
       {
         question: "11 + 1",
         answer: "12"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 2",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 3",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 4",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 5",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 6",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 7",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 8",
         answer: "19"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 9",
         answer: "20"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 10",
         answer: "21"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 11",
         answer: "22"
       },
       {
         question: "11 + 12",
         answer: "23"
       }
     ],
     "12": [
       {
         question: "12 + 1",
         answer: "13"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 2",
         answer: "14"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 3",
         answer: "15"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 4",
         answer: "16"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 5",
         answer: "17"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 6",
         answer: "18"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 7",
         answer: "19"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 8",
         answer: "20"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 9",
         answer: "21"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 10",
         answer: "22"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 11",
         answer: "23"
       },
       {
         question: "12 + 12",
         answer: "24"
       }
     ]
   }
 }